# **DAO QUANG HOAN - Data Scientist**

Via Leonida Bissolati, 26, Mestre, Venice, Italy

**८** +39 3496231251 **■** quanghoandao@gmail.com **%** Webpage: https://quanghoan.github.io/

### **OBJECTIVE**

Hi! My name is Hoan. I was a web developer for about 2 years. Currently, I am master student at University Ca' Foscari of Venice working in the fields of data analysis, machine learning and computer vision. At the moment, I'm open to work, I desire to work and learn in the professional, open and friendly environment, be dynamic to learn and discover more new things from work and people, cultivating major knowledge and soft skills.

### **EDUCATION**

Hanoi University - Vietnam	Sept 2011 - Jun 2015
Major: Information Technology	
Bachelor of Information Technology	
Ca 'Foscari University - Italy	Sept 2017 - 2020

Major: Computer Science

Master's degree in Computer Science - Data Management and Analytics

## **SKILLS**

AI and Data Management	Adversarial Machine Learning, Machine Learning, Neural Networks, Data Mining Algorithms, Data Design
Other skills	Problem-solving, Data Structures and Algorithms skills, Computational Thinking, Open Source, Web Development
Main Languages and Frameworks	Python, R, PHP, SQL, Tensorflow, Keras, scikit-learn

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

SCUTI CO., LTD	June 2016 - Sept 2017
Full Stack Developer	

Development of web applications and web services for B2B and B2C.

# Media Max Japan CO., LTD Nov 2015 - Apr 2016

Full Stack Developer

Development of web applications and web services for B2B and B2C.

#### **PROJECTS**

#### **Kmeans and Spectral Clustering on Image Segmentation**

(Apr 2019 - Aug 2019)

Customer	Prof. Pelillo Marcello
Description	An implementation of k-means and spectral clustering on few UCI datasets. We also use K-means and spectral clustering on the Berkeley Segmentation Benchmark
Team size	1
My position	Data Scientist
My responsibilities	Implement Kmeans and Spectral Clustering on a few datasets
Technologies used	Python, scikit-learn, numpy, pandas

### A Time Series on Global Temperature

# (Feb 2018 - Jul 2018)

Customer	Prof. Carlo Gaetan
Description	Analyze a time series of global temperature of land and ocean to estimate persistent features over 140 years and predict the future
Team size	2
My position	Data Scientist
My responsibilities	Apply filtering to identify trend, verify the stationary and the randomness of the time series, evaluate the data support for different of ARIMA process, make prediction.
Technologies used	R

# **Networks in Economics and Social Science**

(Sep 2017 - Feb 2018)

Customer	Prof. Casarin Roberto
Description	Analyze a dataset of 210 bank networks which is recorded in different time. Base on this dataset, we calculate some statistic indexes for all networks to show the evolution over time
Team size	2
My position	Data Scientist
My responsibilities	Analyze and apply graph theory to dataset to visualize the relation of these banks and the health of each bank
Technologies used	R